From the shadows of the subconscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, true
Trolls de-dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, Trix bringing love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like we awake, can't step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like we awake, can't stop look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
Okay, we're back. Okay. Hey everybody. He goes. Okay, so
How are we doing thank you very much for that very generous donation and
You know Sebastian back up here. Yes
Yes, and so
What's up, but yeah, how do you like the opening you like the opening?
Yeah, yeah, I mean I use a few kinds of AI with it
You know, I think I basically I put in the input for like that song and I'm sorry for being rude
I did donate money. It's your money. Do whatever the fuck you want with it. What I want is I want Sebastian to be up here
I want God to be up here and
Yeah
Body is a bastion come on up and it is open panel them headphones and I've told you this about four times now
But then headphones are they're doing justice for you brother. You like it. Turn your head. Try to not try to head
Yeah, those light up. Yeah, I like it. Yeah, go do it. Yeah, that'd be light up pretty cool
Yeah, I was usually back in the day that you have your room back as fuck. So those headphones. It's like they were so bright
Yeah, it's pretty good pretty good here. Here's Lola. Hey Lola come on. Say hi. Let's say how it goes
Oh my god rewind dude, if you watch this back rewind that her eyes were just fucking red
Yeah
Hi everybody
You're not blocked hi-touch. I don't know why you would I mean there are a lot of people on my ban list
But it's like they're mostly like these really weird names and psyche by the way. I didn't open up. I I was just
Because in what I know was
They were talking shit my eyes not even my boy. They're talking shit to him bullying him in the comments Sebastian
That's why I opened it up. Literally. That's why I put it up like boy. Yeah, let's run it. You know I'm saying
Yeah, I mean, yeah, yeah, I don't know why people are picking on anybody like
He joined and he different himself. He did pretty fucking good
Yeah
Yeah, we give people a chance to defend themselves. They will you know or it's like, you know, I
Basically, I just like you know, I just like I don't need to really defend myself. I feel like I
you know
If I was
I mean, I just thought I mean it's a hard to defend yourself because you don't know what you have but you're defending yourself
But now you know what you have to fuck that thing is like Sebastian. I opened up for ten bucks
Then I gave another fifty. Hey, he has at least six bucks, man. Okay. Well, do you work in that one to the back?
I'm not gonna ask. I'm not gonna ask for it, but
I'm not involved in that. What's your money, dude? Go get some tacos.
Well, I mean, I really
I've been like cleaning up so my house so well. I've been like, you know, getting a lot of cleaning supplies
I've been getting like new stuff for the for the show like, you know, I've got I got five new decks
Five or six like for 25 bucks, you know, I got like a bunch of deck including the Christina Ricci
I talk a lot of shit about tarot cards, but you got some new fucking cards. I'll fucking take a read
Yeah, I got new cards, too. I have my cards right here, too. Do you really like a reading?
I like the uh, I know why I like the animal reading and they're also like this
What do you call a strong up, uh?
Astro
Like a little or not. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, I like the animal reading. I like that one
Well, how about like I can read something about you and love let me see if I can find it home like oh, like yeah
Are you like give a girlfriend or like are you date you date or anything? I can tell you about your sign
And I'm a girl. Wow. We broke up man
So the oh right you're Leo, right? Yeah, I am a Leo. Yeah, but I broke up my girl
Shit this will this what's that I can probably actually she broke up mean you know why
In college brother
Long is that like last one you last relationship you better. I was talking to you literally last month and I have her
Oh, okay. Okay. Gotcha. We're gonna be good. I'm talking about like well
I can like if you give me to your Leo, so I can read about
Can you let God be up here before we do this?
Okay, so I'm looking up Google books. Okay, Google it's on Google books. So I have it here. Okay, so
My library and then it should be right here. Okay
Okay, so
It's not audio book. It's a guy. It's a really it's really funny. I think you like it says so
My my library shit, okay
Okay, and then it's called born on a
Okay, I have this book
Okay, here it is love on a run day. I made a preview of the book
Okay, well I'll go to the other ones. I don't know where all my books went
But yeah, I saw yeah, it's a Leo Leo man in love
So what did you do today?
Well, I may have went to college but I didn't stay
You went to college Amanda stage art DJ I
Yeah, come on up. Yeah. Yeah, right by the way, I have some more cars, you know, I've been like working on some cars
I'm gonna do a ghost car too, but if God is here by him, huh? Okay. I will
There's no backstage yet. Okay, so okay, so here's look. Okay. Got it. Okay. And so read now. Okay. Here we go
Okay, so I'll go to Leo and so here's Leo in love
Okay
It says
Okay, Leo in love
Page
I have more money to open it up how much money nobody's trying to join
Yeah, I mean, yeah, no one's like
No one's gonna join the comments though
There are come on come on guys one electric one. I'm up. It's a nice quiet time. Okay
Let's get to Leo Gemini cancer. Okay, so Leo. Oh, here we go
Hi
Oh, are you good? Yeah, I'm good good
It's been busy, but I miss I miss it here. Oh my god. I miss you, too
Yeah, welcome back
I was about to read go some about a battle Leo. What's your sign a lecture to?
Okay, well
No, no, listen
Yeah
I'm kind of thinking
Thinkin what the circle of life?
I'll read that I read of the lion man. You know, I'm trying to fit some game
Come on now
transfer a little game
How old are you?
I think I might be like
mom's age
Wow, what are you are in your 20s?
No, I'm your mother's age. I'm in my 40s. I'm in my well, I love
Listen, I'm 33 but I love
Okay
I
You know what outside you I love your music by the by the way if you were in here earlier when I paid for the panel
You should have played that shit. We could have fucking I said a fight and get a fist pump
Yeah
Okay, I'm gonna read it
I'm not gonna lie to you. I think I think of the I know
She uses like an average hard button real person, I think she's beautiful
He is beautiful
Beautiful heart too, and I think you both are be are like about warmth of the Leo, you know
No, but I'll read them. Oh, yeah, we both have that lion spirit though
Let's hear what psyche is gonna say about you want to hear me sing? Yeah, what do you want?
Maybe you'll be interested in the Leo man
We're gonna give us something to lecture, okay?
My newest song is
All I want to do is touch it touch it hey hey hey
Hey, I like to touch you, but I ain't yeah
Okay, now let's listen to psyche
It says okay, so that the quote is I make it up all different every time I'm asked Andy Warhol
This is a little man a Leo mayors warm hearted
Leo mayors warm hearted generous and dignified he's a genuine romantic
You won't have to temp twice for it go for moonlight stroll or your favorite hideaway for the weekend the lion see
No, she's not gonna play
Never mind never never mind never mind
No, I want to hear it. I do but okay. Okay already about the already about the female. I read about her
So go go see that show so listen to this if you love one of Leo woman
I'd like to hear the labor one one. Okay. What do you want to do? Why are you here? Why are you here first of all?
Why are you here though, it's my panel dumps lock. Why are you here? Okay? How much did he pay you Si? Did you pay?
He paid me he paid $60. Yeah, okay. Yeah, so he was very
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
You don't want Amanda, but Amanda, I'm gonna read you the Libra
No, fuck that we're gonna have enough them goes we are happy with
Opened up now
If you don't mind, I'm going to read this real quick. Okay. No, no, I don't want to reading. Let's just open. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Come on. Okay. Yeah
I don't want you to have but she shouldn't have you let me fucking read it, please
That is hate
Take my money do whatever you want
Okay, but you said you told me me anything specific go ahead
Okay, so if you love one
Okay, so let me just read it real quick
Going to me
Please do JT because I don't have the strength to argue with him. I just don't
Okay, then why are you here don't fuck? Why are you here?
You don't have the stroke to be here. Why are you here?
Joe because
Goes goes goes come on
I don't have enough strength why why are you never mind never mind good. I can't talk about my own show goes go ahead
Okay, it's my panel don't fuck
Dollars to cut his fucking panel time out. How about that? All right, if she gets me $60. I'll leave
She gives you $60. Yeah, go easy get them signals. I'll leave go ahead
I mean, it's ridiculous.
I'm going to do it.
You are, you don't fucking dump.
OK, OK, OK, it's OK.
I'm going to do it.
It has a lot of fucking account.
You want to you want to compare account?
It's like, if you love one a Libra woman, it says,
everyone should have enough money
to get plastic surgery.
Beverly Johnson.
I'll go with her.
Says she's a sweetheart of the zodiac discriminating thoughtful romantic their minded lovely Lieber's main objective is harmony and a meaningful relationship
She is warm
Sensual feminine you will have to compete with several other artist suitors for her delicate hand. You're lucky someone else will win it
If that's no wife we could stepmother was dangerous and love with her
50 bucks for this I paid 50 bucks to have enough never mind never mind Amanda already too late already too private later
I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't mean I don't
Let's run that bitch, dawg. You want to run it? Let's run that bitch, dawg. Let's run that bitch, dawg. Let's run that bitch, dawg. Let's do it.
Fucking shag it. Let's run it.
Hey, ghost. No, you can't say that on my channel either. Come on.
I can't say that shit. You've already told me I can say it.
Let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let
Yeah, you won't do it. I bet you won't do it. Are you do you know who's not gonna do it you you're not gonna get
Well for sure, I'm not gonna do it, but you know who also is not gonna shut the fuck up
Okay, good back
Let's run it dog
Let's run it bitch. Thank you. Let's run a second. Yeah, they're way doing every way good
We were if you fucking stupid that's got shut up. You're not
You're not smart enough to have the conversation man, what conversation is that?
I'm trying to keep up, but you fucking retard I am trying I am trying
I didn't know we were having a conversation
You didn't understand that they're kind of self-autistic when you don't know what the fuck's going on
Maybe you should sit down and be quiet sir. You ever thought about that?
Is this not my fucking panel I got a pig and you want another 50
Oh, no, you gotta pay another 50 for it to really be yours, but you're right
I do I do kind of look autistic in this picture. Don't I it's like yeah, I don't want them here
If you do another 50, you can kick off whoever you want for the rest of the show.
I already did another 50, Richard, I already did it.
You did it?
Oh my gosh, you did?
No
You're gonna have to do it again. Oh you want another 50 of them like this right just to get rid of me
All right
It'll just be like you can have your how how about the panel you want you can have whoever on you want
Yeah, he's gonna do it again. Hopefully he'll give me he'll give me for like 48 hours gotty
Okay, okay, so I'm making up.
Create.
Go ahead and down it, make sure you're correct.
What are you doing? I'm making it. I'm making it real quick. I'm gonna say just make the best car for her
He's about to drop you another 50. He's definitely drunk the best card like are you pick you're doing G?
I'm doing a car for DT Electra
Okay, like hard like the ones that you're made. Yeah, uh-huh
Yeah, I'm just putting it through right now. I'll show it to you just like it
DJ pickers or do you just picking them for everybody because you picked my any beat as I love that I didn't want to pick mine
I'm thinking I'm thinking I'm just like I'm getting kind of got an idea of what
It should be like the right one. Yeah, so
Yeah, I think I know
Okay, so I'm not gonna keep it a secret. Okay. Okay. I'll be right there
But I also I do have another one. I did the gaudy one God
Love you, okay
So here is oh my gosh
Is he coming back or you pay to kick me like
You said 50 don't be cheap
Okay, well, I know I think that's that's been it's like by $80. So I'll give him the chance
It won't be 24 hour ban. It's just for the rest of the panel until 3 a.m.. Although he didn't say what it was for
That I mean he's nice. I know he keeps forgetting that he's forgetting to put that he doesn't know what he's doing. He's too drunk
He's here under Arbiter
Yeah, he's donating under Arbiter, but he's not even saying what it's for
He doesn't know what he's doing. Yeah, I mean ghosts come up here and boot me off the panel for 24 hours
I mean you're sorry, I just do that to the rest of the show Amanda
I really don't feel well and want to lay down anyway. Okay, sweetie way for you to make money
Yeah, you're becoming quite the pay pig, just like, yeah, congratulations.
No, well, I want to show you a few of the cards I have.
So here's a few of the cards.
Can you guys hear me okay?
So I showed you the Christine.
Okay, so I have the emperor at file.
Oh, did I?
Oh yeah, hold on.
Okay, at file.
The link.
Can you post it?
I couldn't find it.
The link to what?
The link to chat to come up on panel summer wants it. Okay. I'm sorry. Yeah, I got I got some I'm sorry
I thought it was pinned. I thought it was pinned. But oh, yeah, it must not be okay. So
There's that okay, and then I tried to do strength with summer, but then it's like it
It's kind of like doesn't it's kind of a more inspired
You know it's worth it can't get her cats use like right and stuff like that
So it's well, I'll say it's inspired by so he's inspired. It's like a but I'll show you that too, but I
Once again, okay, there's
Okay
Here comes Samar, I think
My oh oh here biggie spunky people
Oh
You always have a big smile
It's called a shitting grin for a reason
What's up fellas and ladies?
Now that he's gone you can probably read the labor one
Okay, yeah, I will okay, so I'll read that for you. Here I come
So he pays you money to be on a panel to not even be on the panel. That's crazy
Okay, okay, so it goes um if you guys know like we can say mother was dangerous in love with her mirror
You never thought of female Libra for a spot in the bathroom along with Venus's smile
The hair to the goddess's love of excess leave their female brandishes are credit card like a lethal weapon
God help you if it's rained for three days or the cat caught with a hairball in the bedroom wrote nothing
Chases away this was a blues like an afternoon of power shopping
She never weighs the chosen cons of anything other than when it's the best time for her next facial. It's not that she's stupid
It's just that
A logical thought rarely makes it through the hairspray to a brain.
By the time she's 60, she'll have more than likely to be silicone from the ankles up,
and her decision-making skills are confined to turning in circle three times and spitting over her left shoulder.
Oh my God!
It's a we, Viva's favorite female favorite word.
In romance, she moves to the bath of the starved hyena, closing in on a limping wheel of peace.
Offer her a cup of coffee. She'll thank you on a date take her on a date
She'll plan a wedding marry her and she'll make a tender affectionate lover for about a week
Then she'll present you with her rule to be useless
For example, you must be willing to help run the house
You must be willing to help you must be what not under any circumstances use her towel or her bathroom
The longer you stick around the longer the list gets finally including your sexual behavior
She will make that can be that can be referred to ghosts. He will cling to you long after you moved out
Even a part, even parting was her idea. She's not pining. She wants to assure herself that you are suffering and will try to exercise her power to call you in a moment's notice for a quickie.
If you're full enough to fall for this and expect any tenderness afterward or perhaps reconciliation, forget it.
By the time you get dressed and back to your place, this Libra will be hot on the scent of her next kill.
Okay, here goes back, okay?
Sorry.
That was it.
Yeah, you're wrong.
I hope you like it. It's kind of like a dark side of it. It's kind of more humorous, but I hope you like it.
Libra women it's a cow dog side is always called a board on a rotten day
And it's like it's kind of like the darker side of the sign so they kind of got in a humorous way
Yeah, it's kind of funny. Yeah, I kind of really like it. It was called change your name from ghost to dork
That's what it was called. Come on
Come on psyche joke around come on
I'll be right back. Let's just run it, you know or somebody crashed with them. I look at the back chat
That's how much of an in-cell he is
Got this woman called you an in-cell
Me no not you
Yeah, these are my girls man, I love them
love them
suck my dick
What was that?
Did he pay to tie me out?
I don't think he did.
My dick goes, pay another 50 bitch and get me off him.
You don't even know what he's doing, man.
I don't even know what he's doing, man.
it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Oh, this is the kind of bitches I get with this is based off of you
I made a card of summer and a few other people
Yeah, okay, so here's here's the emperor hard
Well emperor like as in Star Wars
There we go, that's more fun. Yeah, there we go
Yeah
You're welcome, and then I have a lecture coming next to you if I have
Are you still there
We do one one do one with spunky man. She has that
Are you the wolf man, right?
I just I just you know, I decided to change it up a little bit. I should have had you in oh my god
This is it's a lecture here. I like her left that thing, but I like her. I want her to see this. It's really cool
It looks really really awesome. It's a queen. I'm so here. Okay. Okay. She's here. Okay good
I'll see hers once I get Harman. Electra is not here
Okay, once I get an opportunity to take this one off. Okay
Yes, let's are you there?
Electra look what I got for you. Hopefully she sees it. Okay, so it's white. Wait, wait, wait, wait
Why do you do it that way? Why are you like is she here? I like Electra
Yeah, there's a DJ like
She's like, you know, like air, like the sword, but she, because she reminds me of electricity with her, like, avatar.
So I don't remember.
She's not even Leo, but yeah, I think she's a good queen sword.
Have you ever held a real sword, though? Like, you can't really hold a sword like that.
So heavy.
It's sort of armor in a sword. How does anybody even walk?
I mean, I don't think...
Can I just say how cool that was of Ghost to donate?
What did he just say?
It goes, Ghost, thank you so much, Ghost.
It goes so sweet for you to donate,
but if you want me to get off the panel,
bitch, you need to pay, and you need to pay.
But it specifically depends on how
do I suck my dick from the book?
Wasn't it cool how he forgot to mention
what he was paying for?
Yes, he did, and I'm not body drunk.
You only you only paid 20
Okay
Tell JT about and psyche about fucking how we both have passed out at fucking like
I'm going to be he's going to be partying in hell.
Hey guys, if you can just go saying anything I should be reading back state. I'm almost afraid to look at
Everybody knows that
You know
Like a little brother that you know never shut the
I don't really call him ghost
It was fair and square
Stop trying to scam psyche
Why would you want to give it to me?
I'll give you another
I'll give you
I mean, no, I don't want to give it to you.
Yeah, my 90 you're gone. It's not gone. Don't worry. Don't worry about that. Come on
Come on, brother. Cuz cuz cuz I don't give you in the future. I'll give you your own panel and I will let you
Youngest shit, but I fuck you
I don't know. I don't know this I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this JT guy I don't know this
but he's saying you didn't make up the money apparently
you need to make up the money and the difference and then fucking everybody will be lucky
come on bro run your fucking channel down
dude no no no stop trying to scam him now it's like you didn't do anything wrong here
what do you mean trying to scam I gave a hundred dollars
What?
Like you don't do it to me, bro.
You didn't write nothing on the money!
Like you don't do it!
Don't do it to me, bro!
I'll let you do it. I'll let you do it.
I'll let you do it.
guys okay for that okay for that $20 because i told you i was like you said you said you wanted to
give me 50 i gave you over a hundred don't do this now did you i think that is what yeah that
was the channel though the channel the only one super chair i know i know i know i know okay so
you said the other 20 so you know if we can't agree to something i'll send you 50 oh listen
Okay, yeah, I knew it. Now is then you said you said it wasn't for the panel too, but then I gave you the panel
I am that I said that he said it
How how about I said I'll let you get anybody who went for the panel for the rest of the panel
For tonight for 50 or another 50 and then you sent 20 and so
That's not enough
That was it another
Argument goes I'm gonna make it I'll make sure it's worth your while. I'll give you another panel and everything, okay?
Banner with your name on it, wouldn't that be nice? Yeah
This one it's all give you one better. I'll take this one
That was like an adult thing
He said I'll take this one. Yeah, I can't be over a hundred dollars. I should be able to kill people. Yeah
Wait, wait, wait, you said earlier was like you're like, well, you don't really care who's here or not you just want to just want to make sure
Dude the way I took it is he was basically gonna have one on one
If you were going to kick me for free, I'll go with you.
I'll go with you.
Bitch, you're gone.
Someone's gone.
Take that money.
Pay another $50, bitch!
I'll give you $50.
I already paid you.
Reward him a little more.
You didn't pay him.
He was born.
Don't do that.
Don't do it.
That's like, you know, I could.
That's what it's like.
Come on now.
I'll get a 1v1.
Yeah, I'll go 2.
That's fine.
You and a 1z.
How about that?
You don't really want her to go.
You want summer here.
Come on.
Yeah, you like summer here.
We want summer here.
I want summer here.
Summer is great.
Right after I'm gone.
The money all right summer's back. That's fine. I didn't
Thank you
Money though
I will talk to you five
You came back people motherfucker.
Nah, she's talking shit right now.
She's on her.
I don't want her here.
You know what?
She's gone.
Go, go, go, go.
Hey, don't run.
Give me.
Come on now, man.
I don't want her here.
Come on.
All she does is talk shit.
She don't pay nothing.
No.
That's it.
Come on.
I don't want her to talk shit.
She wouldn't beat you up.
I don't want her here.
I think way more than her.
You gotta kiss me so I can't get it.
You gotta kiss me, you gotta kiss me.
Bye.
So give me my money back
It's a 3 a.m. and
Okay, he's a five minute. He's a five minute to bring you back to bring you back. Okay, I promise.
Five minutes. Okay. Okay. When I am I'll bring you back. That's summer, but we still have sponky
We do
Well
It's very good. I think seriously people are very generous to me. I don't have any complaints about anybody
I think thank you everybody's cool. You're wonderful. Yeah, you all look you are you are a really awesome people
Oh, fuck that because you try to take a you take a hundred dollars from a person and then kick him out
It was 70 and it was it was it you can do math
That's the person who goes out to the super chat thing that you two take 30% of those
Did you give a by the way sir, how much did you give?
How much did you give for a quarter?
You're talking about 70, how much sir?
I don't give a fuck bitch, where are you?
I don't give a fuck bitch
Do you look at the top look up at the top left and look at the pilot
70 dollars he was gonna get a cam session with psyche he's disappointed
You can have one goes you can have a cam session with me. Oh, you got it, okay?
Precamps that's what I want to ask for psyche. So no, no, no, that's that's the cam
It's a fashion back
Okay
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running it. I'm running
Yeah, I did
Are you happy with what you paid for?
I'm not happy with what I paid for
You're not happy
Look at me. I'm happy. Big smile
Look how happy I look
Aren't you the retard that tried to
beat us all to be happy?
He's very sad
Why didn't you show my fucking face?
Why won't you shut the fuck up? She don't know what that you don't mean. No, that was my face. That was my face
Do you know why people in the comments are like hey?
Let's run it
You got a bunch of trolls of here a bunch of bitches of yours run it
what is a crucible go to that phase of this road
that's right, yeah
can we just run it already?
can we just, whatever the fuck that means
can we do that?
you don't know what the fuck you're talking about
can we run it right now?
at all
just run it
yeah, let's run it
are we running it right now?
you don't have to fuck your talking about your troll
why are you here?
What do you mean you're not funny?
Like I now I know why subash where did they ask you're talking to me. Oh, don't you're talking about you're not funny
You're funny
Spongebob
What's wrong that is
What do you do
Hang out with me in the room, so we're now both on gave way too much money
I don't think he gave enough coast. I think you did again
Where he's like you give one guy when you give one dollar sir. He's
Making an even $1, I'll give it on I'll give him you're gonna get monitor right so you're not gonna do it
Are you you're not gonna do it? Are you suspect the fuck you're the one?
dollars
Is it weird that like I said give a dollar and I'll give a hundred
Motherfucker, huh? We're twinning. You know what? If somebody's complaining, I'm gonna ask you if somebody's complaining, I would fucking charge them another 25.
Was it not explained to me that 25? Every time you fucking complain, it should be another 25.
It's like you see that
You know what the burden of proof would be on you
Well, I would like to
I don't know. I don't know.
I
Fuck all y'all, let's rock and run it. I want my money back
I'm gonna get it dumb dumb
I'm dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb
I would be worried about
You don't the fucking you don't the fuck you're talking about. Yeah, you know exactly what we're talking about
Wasn't that generous of him? Yeah, we don't know. Oh, we don't know
I think that was pretty cool you to donate that money
Fucking one versus 40
Fuck it. Let's run it. Go ahead. Yeah, that was cool, man. You didn't even kick anybody down. Let's run that bitch dog
one gets 40
I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't
And then fucking something doesn't work
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello
Is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me or is it me
Hollywood squares, Hollywood squares, Hollywood squares, Hollywood squares, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude
You know what I'm talking about?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahah
This is a better panel.
Thanks, guys.
Thanks for your panel, dude.
We love it.
You're the best, guys.
Dude, wait.
Go swatches and see.
They are.
They're all your girls.
I love them.
Those are the girls I need.
I thought it was going to go a different way for him.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hang on, hang on.
I'm so Justin finally told me in the middle of this dream
that that's a fucking picture of him.
Oh, yeah, it is.
Oh, you didn't know?
Maybe I will say he's the one.
Oh, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God
Ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Yeah
Getting better
I don't know if he's here anymore, are you still here?
He's gone
Dude stop he was gone
Fuck Patrick goes came to control your way out of this
He came through big time for you. He did I appreciate you go city. No ghost. I love it's very generous
Yeah, it was very generous, and I just donated a bunch of memberships to
So they can get back a little nice and everybody wins. Thanks. Go. Yes. Yes
And so, yeah, everyone's looking great.
I love the face I'm seeing.
It's like, I'm a rock set.
I'm a rock set or something.
We just wanted to let you know who was the person that donated to you.
So we're showing our appreciation to the face that donated to you.
That's right.
Yeah, I guess it's about you just a couple hours. Come on. You know, it's like, you know, hey, hey, I was just wondering was what's up with you, man? What's going on?
Who's that? Who's that? Who's that?
Me. I never heard that voice. That's the elbow. I heard a strange voice. Me, too. Me.
That was Ziggy.
No, I'm I don't know
No, somebody put dumb dumb underneath this shit
No idea what the fuck what do you mean?
That was great. Oh dumb dumb
He didn't he said dumb dumb
His battery was down maybe yeah, I love ghosts
We'll get a tarot card. We'll get a tarot card made out of them and all kinds of cool stuff.
Thank you ghost
Yeah, you're so cute, Latin.
Yo, you gotta draw a tarot card of ghosts.
I will.
Never want to hang out with you
Well, that tastes hard. I don't know if I can get a coffee though. It's okay. You definitely can
Okay, whatever whatever you do you got to put it up on the bitch
You can start off drawing like a pig's face and then start making it into ghosts and you'll be go
How pissed off is he right now?
It was nice enough to sponsor this panel and then leave on top of dinner, but he's
That's like
People that are like, I'll block you I'll block I'm never blocked a person in my life
Okay
He was fucking gone because I made sure that it's like you knew this 25 was to block him for 24 hours
He did not do any of that
No
Yeah, he did and then he said five minutes and though that I did it for five minutes and that was it, you know
That's like
That was pretty nice
Look and I'll still give him some pals in the future. All right, you give him like a little banner with his little
Well, yeah, but hey, have you heard of an advertisement JT people do like sense since super they send a TTS with the messages for like $5
You know, it's like a whole show. So it's like
Sikey at the end at the end of the day fucking JT's woman fucking said it very true
He donated. He didn't fucking pay. He donated.
And you are supposed to specify. I mean, of course, I will work with you. If someone's not 100% satisfied, I'll work with him.
We came to 5 minutes.
it's great yeah that's like that that's like if i donate the psyche right and i just give it to
him and then 10 minutes later i decide to to want to ban somebody off of the panel i can't do that
unless i call for exactly yeah because whatever i donate it before that if i didn't specify what it
but no but he does he does specify he said he could do it without what you want for the first ones and then yeah
yeah but he didn't get he didn't get in like the whole
oh is there right now he's in the side shot
no i thought that was pretty cool
come up ghost come up top ghost come up top baby you did great ghost
Come back to go a ghost remember this is your pain come up top
Come get this works come get this work youngster. Let's go. Who is that talking like that? Stay tuned
And you have to go to the bathroom or his phone battery was done
Did you see page questions, page questions said, do I still have time for the one that
I bought yesterday that got P-bombed?
Yeah, well, yeah, I'll give you more I'll give you more time on that too, but I did put I did like remember you came this afternoon
I did like I did that that was like one of the outmests
Yeah, no, you had another hour. Yes, of course. Make sure everyone's satisfied, you know, of course, okay?
So if you know absolutely, I'll give you another hour page whenever you want
Okay, so one sec yeah
Oh
The hangman is coming. It's coming, but it's like I think
Hot Huck is cheated on Q
Yeah
Where did this happen?
today
Like Ozzy died and then the hot pockets cheated on Q. Yeah, I was like do they live together or what?
No, but the point is is that he like made the move all the way across the country to go and see her
That's all he like moved out to go like get with it. Yeah
Yeah, right
I don't know, I don't know the details.
Better question, how did he find out?
I wonder, he's depressed.
He knows it, he knows.
I don't know.
Yikes.
Hey, what's up, Erb?
I'm just catching up, sorry about that.
But, Q is a little tricky guy,
and he could be doing it.
You know what I mean?
You might be foolish guys. I have a I have the I have the crucible ghost card now. Do you want to see the crucible ghost card?
Okay, if it doesn't look like this picture
Here we go, let's take a fucking car. It's gonna be like the gesture of the fool. It's good. I
I love it. Okay, here it goes. So here is Crucible Ghost Hero Card. Woo-hoo!
Ta-da!
Oh, yeah!
Look at that!
Oh, fuck yeah! That's fabulous! That's fucking perfect!
Yo, that's... that's holy!
That's fucking ghost like you!
I don't think ghosts are like ghosts.
Okay!
I don't think those would like that
$80 she said $80
Yeah, what's funny psyche that was actually really fucking funny, dude
that's funny for you man, you're high on drugs and you're drunk
well, I'm not on drugs, you keep saying I'm on drugs
you're always on drugs man, or you're high on something
or you're drunk, no
I'm having a fucking blast with my good girls and my good people
what is wrong with you?
I'm having a depression
the private eyes are watching you
the
I won't be caught dead with you in public. Oh
Imagine summer
We've got some private investigators on you you
Like they would even say
Here your farm there in Florida
Yeah, they're watching you man, they watch you every move man, who's that boys?
Sebastian
Another guy
Are you talking? No, it's JT. I think it's JT now
Oh my god, I know they're weasels man all three of them the three of them are weasels you got to be careful with that
You got to be careful with these guys, okay, you got to watch out for these guys man. They're they're tricky. They're very tricky
Okay, it's the best
This Liz, how are you?
the
Oh
The national here you guys see what he did the short thing when here's Richard Simmons. He played that. What a great. Yes. Yes. Yes
Yes, I saw that you guys watch it. I never even got to see that. Was it really good?
Wasn't really a fan of Richard Simmons, but the Simmons Simmons died right last year. Yeah, he died last year. Yeah
Sick of everybody dying he would sell the ranch
Sebastian or this guy's drunk as a skunk people are sitting off
Drugs he's not making any sense even when somebody like Epstein dies. We don't believe it, you know, we figured
Oh, that's missing footage from right forward
They already know
No, it's not 50 it's 40
Oh, it's 40% Oh, but sometimes I get 60% of selective customers. I work for strike force and I
Only a few customers though
Y'all think that some people have visited the island like really visited there for like legitimate business deals and wasn't
It has a Phoenician temple on the island. That's all you need to know a Phoenician temple. They kind of like yeah
Every single person was there for some weird shit and not not not even one person was there for like our legitimate business there
Well, don't get went there
Goals fuck, of course
As in questions, you know
No question is a no no question
Okay, I got it
Yeah, I want to know I want all their filthy names
Well, they have the flight log. You can look at that that's that's been public a few years ago
And then I don't know that we want a quiet list
Oh the quiet list. Well, I don't know they have the pseudonyms here. They I mean they do handle things like they're doing a lot of weird shit over there
Yeah
I feel like I feel like Seabass is fucking like involved in this, right?
And he keeps interrupting
She has like this underwater like exploring company for the ocean she has some kind of an ocean exploring
Gil say Max Gil say and Gil say Max well like we work with it's like those lanes where they're trying to like this
He's playing with it, right? They're trying to like buy these parts up under the under the ocean stuff and develop under the ocean
I forgot what the drones were going under the ocean. Remember. Yeah. Yeah
Well
Since we all know like what we're talking about let's kind of use cold words to keep saggy channel, you know
Guys more say up the pizza stuff is all say up
Where's his bike, you know, like oh, it's in the basement of the Alamo and so all of a sudden there's a basement to the pizza parlor
Where there's no basement and stuff like that and then there's all the very very bizarre things that people aren't just gonna put photos on their
Facebook of them doing
The Jewish
All over again, the global still take you kindly are you talking about them?
Well, the globe was you can't talk about in real soul. Oh, like you'll
My name right now, what you're the one that brought them up. I did that. I know I know we can't talk about
Why did you bring it up?
that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that
I've never seen
Guys all these drugs you can't go on the pale sober not once
He's saying some crazy shit about what?
He's saying some crazy shit about this Epstein shit, man
He knows and then he's fucking offering fucking 40% on fucking lipo suction every fucking time
Dude, it's nuts
conspiracy theories right
Yeah, but yeah, but did you just say what he just said though?
Did you hear what he just said?
He bought a line, wear it, or bought a line for your guards?
Listen, McGee, times are really tough for Sebastian.
He's gone bankrupt because of Osempic and Manjaro.
Yeah, Osempic and then I'm wondering, okay?
But I'm wondering also...
Give him a break.
Exactly, Spongebob.
But I'm wondering, is it even worse because Epstein died?
Fuck you, good ol' Spongebob.
Spunky.
Weird.
Hey there.
Crazy world, huh?
Crazy world we live in.
Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongebob Spongeb
Oh my god.
We don't let it go to waste.
Wait, wait, wait.
Isn't that like a Jim Carrey thing?
Like didn't your hair like stand up one time?
Not Jim Carrey.
Drew Carrey.
Oh, shit.
Oh, that's it.
Yeah.
Drew Carrey.
Not Drew Carrey.
Mariah Carey.
I don't, I don't need hair gel. I'm good for the sports fans that now steve carry harry carry
That was funny man
Wasn't you carry I thought it was what the fuck was that movie? No, I wouldn't do carry
Yo, you know who's gonna die next
I think Madonna is going to go, that would be great.
Madonna?
Jesus I have
We can get a death cool going
Well, of course for you, you know, she did that black man fucking music video of course
What's wrong with that?
Man's music video, what did you say?
Yeah, she did a music video with it
What video
Papa don't preach. Yeah, that's right. Yeah
What's the problem
Bringing it up like it's an issue she did a
It's a lot more than a music video with the black man. I'm just saying
Would you have bring the conversation up?
Oh, yeah, for sure. So you would say Madonna did a video shoot with a white man and the
Joke or the lack will be what?
What was it with Chappelle said it he said it best he went he went daughter daughter can't sing
OK, I'm doing a good thing though.
I really want to be offended about something,
but you're not giving me anything right now.
You want to be offended?
I do.
I've been to say something about black people right now, you got a birthday coming up too. Oh, okay
And it's not and it's not Papa don't preach by the way, it's like is a mystery. What is that?
Like a prayer like a prayer like a prayer. Yeah, and she's getting a black man, and I thought it was disgusting
Why tell me why?
Why is that disgusting because you can't you you're not supposed to intermix
I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back
What what do you mean?
I was saying from my spot
People of his bugger right now
But you can't say that with you mean wrong through I was
So what are you saying Sebastian you agree with him?
No, no, no, these guys are your friends, right? JT. Aren't you Ziggy's friends?
Aren't you guys bed buddies?
Well, now I think, now I think you're trying to say you agree with it.
JT, I ask you a question. Aren't you bed buddies with Ziggy?
And now you're turning on your own friend, huh?
Who's he?
I knew you're a weasel, JT.
Apparently.
I don't have friends.
I agree with his opinion, but he's allowed to have his opinion.
It's my opinion, it's my opinion, it's my opinion, it's my opinion, it's my opinion, it's my opinion, it's my opinion, it's my opinion, it's my opinion, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
That's that right sensible
But saying that's disgusting
Me out though, I didn't say I don't like black people black friends
Race that's all that's it. If you're saying if you if you have a sister and she fucked a black dude, you would be tired
We all know I am all for interracial marriages, but if Hispanics want to stay with Hispanics
Nobody has an issue if black people want to stay with black people don't have any issues
I don't give a fuck if that's not his thing. I don't really care. You know what I mean? Like it is what it is
I only have one problem with the black thing
May speech make sure you
Is black and I love him with all my heart and my children are mixed but and not everybody that's for them
And that's fine as long as you're not disrespectful. I don't give a fuck
Yeah
Summer you're not allowed to make that know why you need to say it anyway, Ziggy. Why don't you keep some opinions to yourself?
Hey, miss Liz. I wasn't even really talking to you, buddy
I'm talking to you buddy
Everybody's bodies this is called
I don't do interracial. Yes, exactly my body my choice
This is right
that's an abortion. Hey, hey, that's his choice. It's my choice. Yes, I mean, if you want to know
They say it's like white, white, white, white.
And I love being mixed, so holler.
And that's fun, yeah.
He's saying white, like, Stu says cool with white.
I remember, to me, I feel like sometimes people will like it.
Like I said, I don't care if somebody's like, hey, you know what?
I'm going to stay with my race.
That's fine.
To me, that doesn't make them a racist.
Now.
Races, this is gonna be like fuck you. I don't like this person
Yeah, exactly. I have a I have a best friend
I'ma stick my kind and drag down your kind. Yeah, that's right
Now don't double back. Don't don't don't
Wipe on me kissing a black man is disgusting
But that's not going to my point to my point to that
Now summer I think you and your husband are disgusting then he'll get my fucking attention
Yeah, yeah, no, that's when it makes it personal facts. No
Over his own life and what he chooses to do I don't see that racist and I think it's weird
Because when white people when black people say it or Hispanic people say it or any of that other shit
Then nobody has an issue with it. Well, I don't have an issue with white people. They want to be white people
I don't have a problem with that. I do have an issue with white people or any race. That's racist
Yeah
We put all the ghosts down on the bottom bar like all four like in a row
God damn it's like what are you doing, man? You're jerking off back there. No matter of fact
I got I got I got a good one for you. Hold up
You said you would have a problem if your sister fucked a black guy, right?
But is it a problem if you fucked a black girl? Let me ask you
You know, no, I did not say that I said
No, no, no, hold on. I said I might have a problem because obviously that's what I view life in
is with genetics and fucking
right so okay so then you asked me that question if my sister would fucking fucking black guy
i'd have a little bit of a problem with it but guess what the kid might come out and
fucking be cool as shit and then i might have to grow to fucking be cool as an uncle
you understand no problem okay all right so the quite all right so would you fuck a black girl
have
You have so how yeah, so how does that work?
How is it okay for you to fuck a black girl?
But if you had a sister and a black man fucks her that's a problem make that make little little different whenever the woman
conceives the
Yeah, for me that's the way I look at it
But she never got my shit. It wasn't like that it conned them, you know, and I was
But that's it that's what you're saying, but not to procreate what say he's not nothing in her buddy. Yes. Yes, correct
Is correct
Because that's my self-pref, that's my self-preference I do not want to fucking procreate with
Okay, how about how about this like Chinese I like I wouldn't I don't want to do that like nothing
You know, I want to stay
I deal with real fucking racism down here. Okay, and I we don't consider that racist. I'm sorry
No, she's in Kentucky. I was born in West Virginia girl. Yeah
It could be construed as but fuck it. I mean you got your you got your own preferences, right?
I'm nice to my black friends. I'm dude. I have my own I have my own home
I have a black friend that f***ing comes over and visits me from f***ing tech.
Well, just so you know, you're a black friend without a trophy, and just because you have black friends, that doesn't make you racist.
You're not a racist because you're not a racist, or you're a racist because you're a racist.
It's not, it has anything to do with your friends, just a flag.
Oh
Kind of sounds like
Yeah, it does. I know what she's saying, but this black friend now I grew I grew up with him and
Fucking
To each other and I got my own place and fucking he'll come and visit me once a year man
No, no, don't don't don't play that
That's it
Let me explain let me explain I don't think your meaning to be that way like you know what I mean
But like if you're not racist, it's like I'm not racist because I'm not fucking racist. I think it's stupid
I don't give a fuck if I've known people that were white and black and they were prejudice and racist and they were with the opposite race
So that's to me. That's not saying as someone that comes from an interracial family and have the interracial family
Yeah, I didn't I didn't I didn't come from an interracial family
but
No, no, like dude, whatever man. I'm just saying
I know I don't really know how to explain it because fucking they're trying to press me on fucking
How am I racist because I just don't want to put my sperm in a black woman. Why I don't I don't see that racist
I just don't because I know exactly
But like I said, you don't have to say I'm not racist because I have black friends. I'm not racist because I'm not racist
No, okay
I can ask about questions to make it racist
Look look I'm just saying to that fucking like every year my buddy fucking from high
school that I grew up with comes to fucking my fucking house and fucking hangs out because
we were in the military he's a black guy he has a fucking black woman he has fucking
Like dude, you know, that's not if I was racist. I'd be like get the fuck away from me
You never come to my fucking house, you know, that's how I look at it
Where is
Yeah, hold on one second. Let me get the flow for like 10 seconds Justin Boyle
You said I'm a clown. Oh because of people want to stick to their own races
You did not hear you did not hear what he said. He said that he would fuck a black girl
He said he did fuck a black girl no problem, but he has a problem with his shit if he had a sister that fucked a black guy
With genetics
Yes, it doesn't matter. You said you will fuck a black girl no problem, but if you just didn't
And I made a mistake. I made a mistake
Made a mistake
You made a mistake
Fucking a black woman, which one
Black girl okay gosh
way so I give them the link you just don't either don't ask the right questions to make it super race
Ten more dollars go like this. Yeah, I just need ten more and the panel's yours. We'll get we'll go further
the
Thank you everybody everybody can fucking they want right as long as I think he's talking about the heritage
Like he doesn't want to lose the heritage in his family. That's not racist. He just
I'm not dude. I'm not gonna look this is this is the way. All right. Let me let me talk. Let me talk now hold on
You know, I don't like when dudes bang our white girls and they're like yeah, we won't get back at the white man
When did you ever hear when did you hear a black man ever say that?
Go look up porn right now go look up white look up black man bangs bangs white white or black man bangs white girl
That's for the quick to get you on to the video you stupid ass dickhead
Yeah, but that's a mentality with you
That's no no I have to disagree that's not the mentality of all black men that are fucking white sick
It's a lot of them
I don't know any of them
And I know a lot of black guys
That's my point
But it all feels the same
We think Sebastian in it kind of the truth. Oh shit
Ghost that he'll let me join the panel. That's pretty nice
Yeah, everybody wants a link, huh?
Hey, summer. Hey, summer. You got it. You got to let him know all pussy pink and all money is green
Money's green baby
That's for the link
We're going to Waffle House boys
Chicken and waffles
Chicken and waffles. Oh god. He did it again Jesus
to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to
Well, if you think it's better than you kicking me to I'm out. See you only five minutes out of here. Gotty
No, he's only he's only zapping her for five minutes
Got he's a punk anyways. We don't need him
We need ghosts here. Does he do and they'll be back in five minutes. We need Arbiter
He came through many don't need like 120 bucks. I think we got the talking about waffles and now summer's backstage
Fuck good grief, man. He's spending a fortune here tonight
Where are your people at man, what's going on I guess the people they came up here with me they're gonna come up
Well, no, it was for five minutes, right? So you take the greatest UFC fighter that you know, he's gonna have to help
Okay, it goes you delivered
For the beat the thing panel
I don't know so I get your panel. You it's your okay. Well, I was saying I mean it's like you can have her back
I mean as soon as you say but it's like
Summer's asking how long
She would do the same shit to me 152 summer, okay
got you summer is awesome though come on man I think they have been fair with you man you're outstanding
did I say did I say she wasn't awesome what's your argument I'd never made the claim she wasn't
right and by the way no no no you were talking you were talking about fighting
You were talking about fighting
I'm sorry, I'm sorry to feel like debating
that's not me. I'm kind of like him.
And go, some people are not fair to you, man.
They give you a hard time.
Sometimes they give you a hard time.
That's not fair, huh?
Why does everybody keep saying,
like, why are we here?
What the hell is that?
Go, Ziggy, you heard?
Yeah, we beat up each other.
We say that.
I mean, we're men.
That's the way it goes.
Ziggy, you heard?
Ghost why number you know
Ghost you know RK mango
I don't I don't know that name. I don't know that okay. Okay. I think that might be a problem. Maybe yes
No
Join if you're trying to join yeah back stage don't show us. Do not show his face
No, why why can't we see him?
This was the worst mistake
Oh, you scared you scared to death I brought my boys over
the
Why do you keep seeing them down? What's your argument? You gotta pay your fucking rate cuz you're fucking retarded, sir
Would you like me explain it in like little words?
see
Would you like me explain stupid to you cuz I use
Yeah, explain stupid to me. Okay, when you stupid when you know what the fuck's going on
If you're too idiotic, if you're stupid, if you retard it, you know, I'll use all the mid-works for you, brother. I got you.
So, Psyche, this is what we get?
What do you mean, Psyche?
I've been there for the past year. What are you gonna do? What are you gonna do? What are you gonna do?
What are you gonna do about it?
What am I gonna do about what you like to donate money
You're gonna sit there and shut the fuck up the same place over this guy
Just didn't you he said shut the fuck up
Man I have a problem with people
Debate
I
Don't know why he once
Bouncing a wowow bitch I'm back!
Yeah, she's back.
She's back.
Who says honey boo boo talking?
She can be here.
That's a nice one.
It's too loud, psyche.
That's a really nice wallpaper.
Now take a bow out, bitch.
That one gives a fuck what you're saying.
I give a fuck what I say
Identify yourself, bitch.
I got a lot more than you can handle their
Why'd you call her?
I'm going to die paid for this fucking panel
Next time you pay for it, I'll be quiet
Also, I'll put you on a t-shirt
I'm gonna be smoking on you
I'll be smoking all the time here.
Yeah, I got it.
You heard.
I'm sorry.
I can't say where the fuck I want, boy.
Oh my god, they can't say where the fuck I want, boy.
You're going to get a smash in the mouth.
That's the weirdest thing I've ever seen.
That's the worst thing you've ever heard.
Alright, well then, crash me out.
Go ahead and try.
You ain't going to take this back. Crash it out now.
Go ahead.
Yeah, you're not gonna do shit are you bitch?
Fuck you boy, you can say they were all you want
You just be quiet down there
You and you both are
Miner talk it
You heard?
Now fuck around, go soft fuck around.
I'm going to take the detectives.
Shut up.
No one cares what he says.
No one cares about your stupid opinions.
No one wants to hear you talk.
Why are you talking to me somewhere?
Yeah
No, no, summer's nice. She's nice
Go
You're not man enough to do it sir. You're not man enough to do it sir. You're not man enough to me to check
Let's run that bitch
god damn why are you running your fucking mouth
shut the fuck up
can you take your card off so I can see the names on the panel
because I don't know who this purple voice is
it's not your panel we've already psyched the panel
what the fuck is that
no I'm not gonna shut the fuck up
you better recognize the name you're on
You better pay some more money and shut me the fuck up bitch!
You and your flunky ass fucking friend!
Fuck both of you non-fucking nuts!
Have another fuck with me!
Fuck both of you motherfuckers!
This train doesn't have a name!
Suck my dick! Suck my dick from the back of the 20-bit!